delorie.com 2001-02-04

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement** Our basic policy is that we don't care who you are, but we keep track of what you do with our machines, and you will be responsible for anything you ask us to publish on your behalf. 

## Forms

This web site makes a reasonable effort to refrain from disclosing information submitted via forms. We cannot guarantee that accidents won't happen. If you are concerned about privacy and are unwilling to take the risk, simply do not provide your information. Private information is never a requirement for services provided here. 

## Browsing

The mere act of viewing pages on this site will not cause private information about you to be recorded. We do, however, record your IP address, the date and time your browse each page, and the URL of the page. We normally do not make this information available to the public - it is collected to provide statistical information about server usage, and to plan for future capacity. We may occasionally use "cookies" to temporarily identify your session in order to improve the quality of service we provide, but such cookie use will not cause any personal information about you to be disclosed to us. 

## EMail

Any information mailed to any of the mailing lists hosted by delorie software is considered public information and will be archived and disclosed to the public. Some services may require an email address to verify authenticity (for example, services whereby the user submits information which is maintained by delorie.com, such as the HOWTOs) and in such cases the email address will be published with the submitted information, to allow readers to contact the authors. 

## Banner Ads

Banner ads appearing on this site have their own privacy policies provided by the banner ad agents. See [Burst! Media](http://www.burstmedia.com/privacy.htm) and [Flycast](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html). 

## Other

Send email to [dj@delorie.com](mailto:dj@delorie.com) if you have further questions about this policy. 

_Please take a moment to fill out this[visitor survey](http://38.148.250.3/cgi-win/client.exe?Burst,welcome,ad1954a,2000)_

_You can help support this site by visiting the advertisers that sponsor it! (only once each, though)_
**Privacy Statement** Our basic policy is that we don't care who you are, but we keep track of what you do with our machines, and you will be responsible for anything you ask us to publish on your behalf. 

## Forms

This web site makes a reasonable effort to refrain from disclosing information submitted via forms. We cannot guarantee that accidents won't happen. If you are concerned about privacy and are unwilling to take the risk, simply do not provide your information. Private information is never a requirement for services provided here. 

## Browsing

The mere act of viewing pages on this site will not cause private information about you to be recorded. We do, however, record your IP address, the date and time your browse each page, and the URL of the page. We normally do not make this information available to the public - it is collected to provide statistical information about server usage, and to plan for future capacity. We may occasionally use "cookies" to temporarily identify your session in order to improve the quality of service we provide, but such cookie use will not cause any personal information about you to be disclosed to us. 

## EMail

Any information mailed to any of the mailing lists hosted by delorie software is considered public information and will be archived and disclosed to the public. Some services may require an email address to verify authenticity (for example, services whereby the user submits information which is maintained by delorie.com, such as the HOWTOs) and in such cases the email address will be published with the submitted information, to allow readers to contact the authors. 

## Banner Ads

Banner ads appearing on this site have their own privacy policies provided by the banner ad agents. See [Burst! Media](http://www.burstmedia.com/privacy.htm) and [Flycast](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html). 

## Other

Send email to [dj@delorie.com](mailto:dj@delorie.com) if you have further questions about this policy. 

_Please take a moment to fill out this[visitor survey](http://38.148.250.3/cgi-win/client.exe?Burst,welcome,ad1954a,2000)_

_You can help support this site by visiting the advertisers that sponsor it! (only once each, though)_
